let questions = [
    {
     question: 'What year did Lisa graduate from college?',
   choices: {
        a: '1963',
        b: '2005',
        c: '1984',
        d: '2013'
   }, correct: 'c'
 },
     {
     question: 'How many times did Lisa move before she was 19?',
   choices: {
        a: 'Less than two',
        b: 'Over five',
        c: 'Not at all',
        d: 'More than 15'
   }, 
        correct: 'd'
 },
     {
     question: 'In which branch of military service did Lisa serve?',
   choices: {
        a: 'USMC',
        b: 'USAF',
        c: 'Coast Guard',
        d: 'Army'
   },   correct: 'b'
 },
     {
     question: 'Which profession does NOT belong?',
   choices: {
        a: 'Networking Engineer',
        b: 'Sales Technical Instructor',
        c: 'Targets Intelligence',
        d: 'Toy Store Manager',
        e: 'Technical Writer'
   },   correct: 'a'
 },
     {
     question: 'Which country has Lisa NOT lived in?',
   choices: {
        a: 'Germany',
        b: 'Canada',
        c: 'Iran',
        d: 'Iraq',
        e: 'South Korea'
   },   correct: 'd'
 },
     {
     question: 'How many children does Lisa have?',
   choices: {
        a: 'None',
        b: 'Two boys and a girl',
        c: 'Four girls',
        d: 'Four boys',
        e: 'One girl'
   },   correct: 'c'
 },
     {
     question: 'What are the ages of her children?',
   choices: {
        a: '12, 13, 20, 29',
        b: 'No kids',
        c: '27, 28, 29',
        d: '12',
        e: '5, 9, 15, 30'
   },   correct: 'a'
 },
     {
     question: 'Which of the following is NOT true?',
   choices: {
        a: 'Lisa has driven a Soviet tank',
        b: 'Lisa has flown in a helicopter',
        c: 'Lisa has visited Pompeii',
        d: 'Lisa has won the lottery',
        e: 'Lisa has visited Panama'
   },   correct: 'e'
 },
      {
     question: 'How many cats does Lisa have?',
   choices: {
        a: 'None, she hates cats',
        b: 'One spoiled cat',
        c: 'Two spoiled cats',
        d: 'Six spoiled cats',
        e: 'Twelve ignored cats'
   },   correct: 'd'
 },
      {
     question: 'How much fun did Lisa have with this quiz?',
   choices: {
        a: 'None',
        b: 'Too much',
        c: 'Not enough',
        d: 'Just enough',
   },   correct: 'b'
 },
 ]